A Guide to the Population Council records, Accession 1, RG 1 FA210
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1
  - Grant Files, 1958-1966; 2
    - Grant # M62.30 - Planned Parenthood Center of Los Angeles, Inc.: Effects of Progestational Steroids on Fertility (Box 47, Folder 679)
    - Grant # M62.31 - State and University Maternity Hosp., Greece: Anti-Fertility Agents Studies (Box 47, Folder 680)
    - Grant # M62.32 - Temple University: Margulies Contraceptive Coil Studies (Box 47, Folder 681)
    - Grant # M62.33 - Temple University: Effects of Nucleic Acids on Gametes (Box 47, Folder 682)
    - Grant # M62.34 - Weizmann Inst. of Science, Israel: Immunologic Studies of Human Gonadotrophins (Box 47, Folder 683)
    - Grant # D62.35 - Brown University: Biometrics of Fertility (Box 48, Folder 684)
    - Grant # M62.36 - Weizmann Inst. of Science, Israel: Support of Research in Reproductive Physiology (Box 48, Folder 685-686)
    - Grant # D62.37 - Bureau of the Census (U.S.): Distribution of 1960 Census Samples (Box 48, Folder 687-688)
    - Grant # D62.38 - Pakistan Inst. of Development Eco.: Demographic Program (Box 48, Folder 689)
    - Grant # D62.39 - Academy for Village Development, E. Pakistan: Family Planning Research (Box 48, Folder 690)
    - Grant # D62.40 - Harvard University: India Population Study (Box 48, Folder 691-692)
    - Grant # D62.41 - United Nations: Support of DTRC in Bombay (Box 48, Folder 693)
    - Grant # D62.42 - University of Ceylon: Population and Fertility Trends (Box 48, Folder 694-695)
    - Grant # D62.43 - University of Athens: Demographic Office (Box 48, Folder 696)
    - Grant # D62.44 - University of Turin, Italy: Demographic History of Lombardy (Box 48, Folder 697-698)
    - Grant # D62.45 - London School of Economics: General Purposes (Box 48, Folder 699)
    - Grant # D62.46 - Princeton University: African Demography Research Program (Box 48, Folder 700)
    - Grant # D62.47 - Princeton University: Fertility in U.S. Metropolitan Areas (Box 48, Folder 701)
    - Grant # D62.48 - Conf. on Eco. and Demo. Change, NY: Expenses (Box 48, Folder 702)
    - Grant # M62.49 - University of Alberta: Lobectomized Rhesus Monkeys (Box 48, Folder 703)
    - Grant # M62.50 - University of Arkansas: Preservation of Human Spermatozoa (Box 48, Folder 704)
    - Grant # M62.51 - Emory University: Flagellar Wave of Spermatozoa (Box 48, Folder 705)
    - Grant # M62.52 - Emory University: Gonadotrophin Levels in Women (Box 48, Folder 706)
    - Grant # M62.53 - Foundation for Endocrine Study, Argentina: Estrogen Level Determinations (Box 49, Folder 707)
    - Grant # M62.54 - Hebrew University, Israel: Effect of Seminal Plasma Proteins (Box 49, Folder 708)
    - Grant # M62.55 - Indian Cancer Research Centre, India: Physiology of Reproduction Studies (Box 49, Folder 709)
    - Grant # M62.56 - University of Kentucky: Male Rabbit Fertility Studies (Box 49, Folder 710)
    - Grant # M62.57 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: IUCD Studies (Box 49, Folder 711)
    - Grant # M62.58 - University of Pennsylvania: Early Mammalian Embryos Studies (Box 49, Folder 712)
    - Grant # M62.59 - Sloan-Kettering Inst. for Cancer Research: Effects of Cadmium Study (Box 49, Folder 713)
    - Grant # M62.60 - Toho University, Japan: Tubal Staples Under Culdoscopy (Box 49, Folder 714)
    - Grant # M62.61 - W. Virginia University: Effects of Anti - Sperm Colostrum (Box 49, Folder 715)
    - Grant # M62.62 - Yale University: Ovum Implantation and Development (Box 49, Folder 716)
    - Grant # M62.65 - University of Birmingham, Eng.: Study of Gonadal Studies (Box 49, Folder 717)
    - Grant # M62.66 - Boston Lying-in Hospital: IUCD Acceptability Studies (Box 49, Folder 718)
    - Grant # M62.67 - University of Buffalo: Cervical Mucus Studies (Box 49, Folder 719)
    - Grant # M62.68 - Hebrew University, Israel: Auditory Stimuli on Reproduction (Box 49, Folder 720)
    - Grant # M62.69 - Kumamoto University: Immunologic Induction of Infertility (Box 49, Folder 721)
    - Grant # M62.70 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Constituents of Human Sperm (Box 49, Folder 722)
    - Grant # M62.71 - University of Hamburg, W. Ger.: Gonadotrophin Studies (Box 49, Folder 723)
    - Grant # D62.72 - NYU Medical Center: IUCD Study (Box 49, Folder 724)
    - Grant # M63.73 - Rock Reproductive Clinic, Mass.: Spermiogenesis Studies (Box 49, Folder 725)
    - Grant # M62.74 - University of Sydney, Australia: Oestrogen and Anti-Oestrogen Studies (Box 49, Folder 726)
    - Grant # M62.75 - University of Washington: Effects of Antimetabolites (Box 49, Folder 727)
    - Grant # M62.76 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Carbonic Anhydrase and Implantation Inhibition Studies (Box 49, Folder 728)
    - Grant # D62.77 - NCMH: General Program (Box 49, Folder 729)
    - Grant # D62.78 - JCRR, Taiwan: Family Planning Program (Box 49, Folder 730)
    - Grant # D62.79 - Columbia University: Assembly on Population Dilemma (Box 49, Folder 731-732)
    - Grant # D62.80 - American Eugenics Society: General Purposes (Box 49, Folder 733)
    - Grant # D62.81 - Population Association of America: Permanent Committee on Population Statistics (Box 49, Folder 734)
    - Grant # D62.82 - University of Notre Dame: Inter-Faith Symposium (Box 49, Folder 735)
    - Grant # D62.83 - Sociedade... Japonesa: Japanese Population in Brazil (Box 49, Folder 736-737)
    - Grant # D62.84 - U.N. - CELADE, Chile: Comparative Fertility Surveys (Box 50, Folder 738)
    - Grant # M62.86 - University of El Salvador: Social Anthropology Program (Box 50, Folder 739-740)
    - Grant # M62.87 - Pakistan Inst. of Development Eco.: Population Growth in Pakistan (Box 50, Folder 741)
    - Grant # G63.1-1 - Michigan State University: Fertility in Man (Box 50, Folder 742)
    - Grant # G63.1-2 - University of Basel: Travel Funds for Colloquim (Box 50, Folder 743)
    - Grant # G63.1-3 - Creedmoor State Hospital, NY: Sterilization in Cases of Huntington's Chorea (Box 50, Folder 744)
    - Grant # D63.4 - Population Reference Bureau: General Corporate Purposes (Box 50, Folder 745)
    - Grant # D63.5 - American Public Health Association: General Purposes (Box 50, Folder 746-747)
    - Grant # D63.6 - University of Chicago: Rural South Family Planning Program (Box 50, Folder 748)
    - Grant # D63.7 - University of Puerto Rico: Surgically Sterilized Men - Follow-Up Study (Box 50, Folder 749-750)
    - Grant # D63.8 - Book, Equipment and Publication Fund: * (Box 50, Folder 751)
    - Grant # D63.9 - University College of the West Indies: Social Stratification in British Guiana (Box 50, Folder 752)
    - Grant # D63.10 - Hebrew University, Israel: Fertility Study (Box 50, Folder 753)
    - Grant # D63.11 University of the Philippines: Statistical Center (Box 50, Folder 754)
    - Grant # M62.12 - Albert Einstein Medical Center, Penn.: Testicular Cells in Culture (Box 50, Folder 755)
    - Grant # M63.13 - Boston Lying-In Hospital: Reproductive Physiology (Box 50, Folder 756)
    - Grant # M63.14 - University of Buenos Aires: Histoimmunological Studies of Human and Animal Testes (Box 50, Folder 757)
    - Grant # M63.15 - UCLA: Purification Studies on Human Chorionic Gonadotrophin (Box 50, Folder 758)
    - Grant # M63.16 - Emory University: Purification and Separation of Human Urinary Gonadotrophins (Box 50, Folder 759)
    - Grant # M63.17 - University of Georgia: Biochemical Aspects of Reproduction (Box 51, Folder 760)
    - Grant # M63.18 - McGill University, Canada: Spermatogenesis in the Rat (Box 51, Folder 761)
    - Grant # M63.20 - Mt. Sinai Hospital, NY: Research in Clinical Conception Control Studies (Box 51, Folder 762)
    - Grant # M63.21 - National Inst. for Research in Dairying, Eng.: Fertility Control Studies (Box 51, Folder 763)
    - Grant # M63.22 - University of Paris: 19 - norsteroids Study (Box 51, Folder 764)
    - Grant # M63.23 - The Rockefeller Institute: Maintenance of Pregnancy (Box 51, Folder 765)
    - Grant # M63.24 - Vanderbilt University: Grafenberg Ring Studies (Box 51, Folder 766)
    - Grant # M63.25 - University of Vermont: Corpus Luteum Studies (Box 51, Folder 767)
    - Grant # M63.26 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Testicular Status and Blood Testosterone Levels (Box 51, Folder 768)
    - Grant # M63.27 - University of Chile: Effect of Gestagen in Human Uterine Contractility (Box 51, Folder 769)
    - Grant # M63.28 - Keio University, Japan: Gestagen's Effects (Box 51, Folder 770)
    - Grant # M63.29 - Planned Parenthood Assoc., San Francisco: IUD Studies (Box 51, Folder 771)
    - Grant # D63.30 - Ministry of Health and Social Welfare, Pakistan: Family Planning Activities and Organizations (Box 51, Folder 772-776)
    - Grant # D63.30-1 - UCLA: Public Health Education Research Project at Dacca, East Pakistan (Box 51, Folder 777)
    - Grant # D63.31 - University of Chicago: Support of a Workshop (Box 51, Folder 778)
    - Grant # D63.32 - United Nations: Support of a DTRC in Cairo, U.A.R. (Box 51, Folder 779)
    - Grant # D63.33 - United Nations: DTRC for Asia and the Far East (Box 51, Folder 780)
    - Grant # D63.34 - United Nations: Asian Population Conference (Box 52, Folder 781-782)
    - Grant # D63.35 - Pakistan Inst. for Development Eco.: Population Growth Rate Study (Box 52, Folder 783-785)
    - Grant # D63.36 - Council for Sciences of Indonesia: Family Life Field Study in East Java (Box 52, Folder 786)
    - Grant # D63.37 - University of the Philippines: Pilot Study of Imus Municipality (Box 52, Folder 787-788)
    - Grant # D63.38 - University of the Philippines: Vital Statistical Rates and Causes of Death in Santa Rosa (Box 52, Folder 789)
    - Grant # D63.39 - JCRR, Taiwan: Family Planning in Taichung City (Box 52, Folder 790)
    - Grant # D63.40 - Ministry of Health and Social Assistance, Turkey: Establishment of a Population Planning Program (Box 52, Folder 791)
    - Grant # D63.41 - Salvadoran Demographic Assoc., El Salvador: Family Planning Study (Box 52, Folder 792)
    - Grant # D63.42 - Hospital Municipal Rawson, Argentina: Criminal Abortion Study (Box 52, Folder 793-794)
    - Grant # D63.43 - Ohio State University: Errors in the 1960 Census (Box 52, Folder 795)
    - Grant # D63.44 - IUSSP, Belgium: Members' Travel Costs for Ottawa Meeting (Box 52, Folder 796)
    - Grant # M63.45 - Albert Einstein College of Medicine: IUD Acceptability, Safety and Effectiveness Studies (Box 52, Folder 797)
    - Grant # M63.46 - University of California - S.F.: Effects of IUD on Rat Fertility (Box 52, Folder 798)
    - Grant # M63.47 - Columbia University: Evaluation of IUD's (Box 52, Folder 799)
    - Grant # M63.48 - Harbor General Hospital, California: Mechanism of Action of the IUD in Primates (Box 52, Folder 800)
    - Grant # M63.49 - Medical Research Foundation of Oregon, Inc.: IUD Studies (Box 52, Folder 801)
    - Grant # M63.50 - NY Medical College: Effects of the Human Endometrium (Box 52, Folder 802)
    - Grant # M63.51 - Australian National University: Endocrine Studies on Marsupial Reproduction (Box 52, Folder 803)
    - Grant # M63.52 - Yale University: Ovum Implantation Interference (Box 52, Folder 804)
    - Grant # M63.53 - Kommunehospitalet, Denmark: Maintenance Factors of Human Gestation (Box 52, Folder 805)
    - Grant # M63.54 - University of Lund, Sweden: Progesterone Rate in Pregnancy (Box 52, Folder 806)
    - Grant # M63.55 - Cornell University: Quantitative Cytological Analyses (Box 53, Folder 807)
    - Grant # M63.56 - Karolinska Inst., Sweden: Human Seminal Fluid Studies (Box 53, Folder 808)
    - Grant # M63.57 - Seoul National University, Korea: Vasectomies in Experimental Animals (Box 53, Folder 809)
    - Grant # M63.58 - College de France: Control of Ovulation (Box 53, Folder 810)
    - Grant # M63.59 - Inst. of Psychiatry, England: Neural Control of Corpus Luteum Function (Box 53, Folder 811)
    - Grant # M63.60 - University of Uppsala, Sweden: Human Pituitary Studies (Box 53, Folder 812)
    - Grant # M63.62 - University of Brazil: Distribution of Antigens in Spermatozoa (Box 53, Folder 813-814)
    - Grant # M63.63 - Magee-Women's Hospital, Pennsylvania: Immune Mechanisms in Pregnancy (Box 53, Folder 815)
    - Grant # M63.64 - University of British Columbia: Antiestrogenic Compounds (Box 53, Folder 816)
    - Grant # M63.65 - Niigata University, Japan: Ovulation Studies (Box 53, Folder 817)
    - Grant # D63.66 - Ministry of Health and Social Assistance, Turkey: Population and Family Planning Survey (Box 53, Folder 818)
    - Grant # D63.67 - Bureau of Research and Statistics, Korea: Development of Population Projections (Box 53, Folder 819-820)
    - Grant # D63.68 - Ministry of Health and Social Affairs, Korea: Consultant on Manufacture of Contraceptives (Box 53, Folder 821-822)
    - Grant # D63.69 - PPFK (Korea): Coordination of a Large Scale Urban Family Planning Project (Box 53, Folder 823-824)
    - Grant # D63.70 - Seoul National University, Korea: Establishment of a Demo. Library (Box 53, Folder 825)
    - Grant # D63.71 - University of Washington: Stipend and Travel Funds for J.Y. Peng (Box 53, Folder 826)
    - Grant # M63.72 - PPFK (Korea): IUCD Studies (Box 53, Folder 827)
    - Grant # D63.73 - Ministry of Health and Welfare, Tunisia: Experimental Program in Family Planning (Box 54, Folder 828-830)
    - Grant # D63.74 - Ministry of Health and Social Assistance, Turkey: Program Consultant in Family Planning (Box 54, Folder 831)
    - Grant # D63.75 - Pakistan Inst. of Development Eco.: Services of a Demographic Advisor (Box 54, Folder 832)
    - Grant # D63.76 - Pakistan Academy for Rural Development: Evaluation of Family Planning Activities (Box 54, Folder 833)
    - Grant # D63.77 - University of Ceylon: Field Study of Differential Fertility Trends (Box 54, Folder 834)
    - Grant # D63.78 - University of Ghana: Program of Teaching and Research in Demography (Box 54, Folder 835-837)
    - Grant # D63.79 - University of Tunis, Tunisia: Training in Demography (Box 54, Folder 838-839)
    - Grant # D63.80 - JCRR, Taiwan: Family Planning Services (Box 54, Folder 840)
    - Grant # D63.81 - University of Chile: Studies of the Incidence of Induced Abortion (Box 54, Folder 841)
    - Grant # D63.82 - U.S. Conf. of the World Council of Churches: Consultation on Responsible Parenthood in Asia (Box 55, Folder 842)
    - Grant # D62.83 - University of Michigan: East Asian Population Studies (Box 55, Folder 843-844)
    - Grant # D63.84 - Community and Family Study Center, Illinois: Summer Workshop (Box 55, Folder 845-846)
    - Grant # D63.85 - Selected Universities (U.S.): Graduate Demographic Students (Box 55, Folder 847)
    - Grant # M63.86 - Beth-El Hospital, NY: IUCD Study (Box 55, Folder 848)
    - Grant # M63.87 - Boston Lying-in Hospital: IUCD Study (Box 55, Folder 849)
    - Grant # M63.88 - Charlotte-Mecklenburg Health Department, NC: IUCD Acceptability Study (Box 55, Folder 850)
    - Grant # M63.89 - Family Planning Assoc. of Ceylon: Clinical Trials on IUCD's (Box 55, Folder 851-852)
    - Grant # M63.90 - Family Planning Assoc. of Hong Kong: IUCD Studies (Box 55, Folder 853)
    - Grant # M63.91 - Inter. Planned Parenthood Federation, NY: IUCD Studies (Box 55, Folder 854)
    - Grant # M63.92 - JCRR, Taiwan: IUCD Follow-Up Study (Box 55, Folder 855)
    - Grant # M63.93 - Planned Parenthood Center, Los Angeles: IUCD Effectiveness (Box 55, Folder 856)
    - Grant # M63.94 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Clinical Study of IUCD's (Box 55, Folder 857)
    - Grant # M63.95 - NCMH: Statistical Evaluation of IUCD's (Box 55, Folder 858-859)
    - Grant # M63.96 - NYU Medical Center: IUCD Study (Box 55, Folder 860)
    - Grant # M63.97 - Ohio State University: Clinical Evaluation of IUCD (Box 55, Folder 861)
    - Grant # M63.98 - Pennsylvania Hospital: Brush Endometrial Smears (Box 55, Folder 862)
    - Grant # M63.99 - Planned Parenthood Assoc., Illinois: Clinical Study of IUCD's (Box 55, Folder 863)
    - Grant # M63.100 - Planned Parenthood Center, Buffalo: IUCD Evaluation (Box 55, Folder 864)
    - Grant # M63.101 - Temple University: Effect of Coil on Cervix (Box 55, Folder 865)
    - Grant # M63.102 - University of Arkansas: Uterine Reaction to IUCD's (Box 55, Folder 866)
    - Grant # M63.103 - UCLA: Clinical Appraisal of Intra-Uterine Spiral (Box 55, Folder 867)
    - Grant # M63.104 - University of Michigan: IUCD Studies (Box 55, Folder 868)
    - Grant # M63.105 - University of Michigan: IUCD Study (Box 55, Folder 869-870)
    - Grant # M63.106 - University of Michigan: Influence of Margulies Spiral (Box 55, Folder 871)
    - Grant # M63.107 - University of Puerto Rico: IUCD Studies (Box 55, Folder 872)
    - Grant # M63.108 - University of Zulia, Venezuela: IUCD Study (Box 55, Folder 873)
    - Grant # M63.109 - Columbia University: Studies on Malucidin (Box 55, Folder 874)
    - Grant # M63.110 - Dalhousie University, Nova Scotia: Decidual Reaction Studies (Box 55, Folder 875)
    - Grant # M63.111 - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, Mass.: Role of Oxytocin in Fertility (Box 55, Folder 876)
    - Grant # M63.112 - University of Sydney: Estrogen Studies (Box 55, Folder 877)
    - Grant # M63.113 - Weizmann Inst. of Science, Israel: Mechanism of Nidation (Box 55, Folder 878)
    - Grant # M63.114 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Implantation Inhibition Studies (Box 55, Folder 879)
    - Grant # M63.115 - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology: Spermatozoa Studies (Box 55, Folder 880)
    - Grant # M63.116 - University of Pennsylvania: Embryo Studies (Box 55, Folder 881)
    - Grant # M63.117 - University of Bahia, Brazil: Physiology of Reproduction (Box 55, Folder 882)
    - Grant # M63.118 - McGill University, Canada: Gonadotrophin Studies (Box 55, Folder 883)
    - Grant # M63.119 - University of Birmingham, Eng.: Gametogenesis Studies (Box 55, Folder 884)
    - Grant # M63.120 - University of Tokyo: Hypothalamic Control Studies (Box 55, Folder 885)
    - Grant # M63.121 - Cuyo University, Argentina: Studies of Mechanism of Sperm Release (Box 56, Folder 886)
    - Grant # M63.122 - Rock Reproductive Clinic, Mass.: Spermiogenesis Studies (Box 56, Folder 887)
    - Grant # M63.123 - Kumamoto University, Japan: Infertility Studies (Box 56, Folder 888)
    - Grant # M63.124 - Foundation for Endocrine Study, Argentina: Estrogen Studies (Box 56, Folder 889)
    - Grant # M63.125 - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, NY: Annotated Bibliography (Box 56, Folder 890)
    - Grant # M63.126 - National Taiwan University: Endocrine Studies (Box 56, Folder 891)
    - Grant # D63.127 - Princeton University: Program of Research on African Demography (Box 56, Folder 892)
    - Grant # D64.1 - University of Wisconsin: Genetics and Population Characteristics (Box 56, Folder 893)
    - Grant # D64.5 - Yonsei University, Korea: Family Planning Research Pilot Study (Box 56, Folder 894)
    - Grant # D64.6 - Ministry of Interior, Taiwan: Evaluation of Household Registration System (Box 56, Folder 895-896)
    - Grant # D64.7 - University of Philippines: Visiting Professor (Box 56, Folder 897-898)
    - Grant # D64.8 - Family Planning Federation of Japan: Book and Equipment Fund (Box 56, Folder 899)
    - Grant # D64.9 - Silliman University, Philippines: Attitudes of Government Workers Toward Family Planning (Box 56, Folder 900-901)
    - Grant # D64.10 - National Research Council, Thailand: Resident Advisor (Box 56, Folder 902)
    - Grant # D64.11 - University of Chicago: Community and Family Study Center (Box 56, Folder 903-905)
    - Grant # D64.12 - University of Pennsylvania: Catholic Fertility (Box 57, Folder 906)
    - Grant # D64.13 - M.I.T. (Mass.): Conf. in Demographic Analysis (Box 57, Folder 907-908)
    - Grant # D64.14 - Foreign Policy Assoc., Inc.: Publication Of INTERCOM (Box 57, Folder 909-910)
    - Grant # T64.15 - Ministry of Health and Social Affairs, Korea: Resident Advisor (Box 57, Folder 911)
    - Grant # T64.16 - PPFK (Korea): Training and Education Program (Box 57, Folder 912)
    - Grant # T64.17 - PPFK (Korea): Urban Research (Box 57, Folder 913-916)
    - Grant # T64.18 - JCRR, Taiwan: Family Planning Action Program (Box 57, Folder 917)
    - Grant # M64.20 - Nagasaki University: Flavonoid Compounds Study (Box 57, Folder 918)
    - Grant # M64.21 - Facult de Mdecine de Paris: Hormone Study (Box 57, Folder 919)
    - Grant # M64.22 - UCLA: Urinary Pregnancy Antigens (Box 57, Folder 920)
    - Grant # M63.23 - National Inst. for Research in Dairying, Eng.: Cervical Mucin Studies (Box 57, Folder 921)
    - Grant # M64.24 - University of Georgia: Fertilization Studies (Box 57, Folder 922)
    - Grant # M64.26 - New England Center Hospital: Enzyme Morphology Studies (Box 58, Folder 923)
    - Grant # M64.27 - University of Bahia, Brazil: Pregnancy Studies (Box 58, Folder 924)
    - Grant # M64.28 - Gunma University, Japan: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 925)
    - Grant # M64.29 - Cornell University: Bow IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 926)
    - Grant # M64.30 - Ryder Memorial Hospital, Puerto Rico: IUCD Field Studies (Box 58, Folder 927-928)
    - Grant # M64.31 - Research Foundation of SUNY, Buffalo: Cervical Mucus Studies (Box 58, Folder 929)
    - Grant # M64.32 - University of Mass.: Spermatozoa Studies (Box 58, Folder 930)
    - Grant # M64.33 - Exeter and District Women's Welfare Assoc.: IUCD Studies in Devon, England (Box 58, Folder 931)
    - Grant # M64.34 - F.P.A. of Trinidad: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 932-933)
    - Grant # M64.35: Film on the Physiology of Reproduction (Box 58, Folder 934)
    - Grant # D64.37 - Pakistan Inst. of Development Eco.: Demographic Advisor (Box 58, Folder 935)
    - Grant # D64.38 - U.N.- CELADE: Fertility Studies (Box 58, Folder 936)
    - Grant # D64.39 - University of Notre Dame: Study of England's Catholic Advisory System (Box 58, Folder 937)
    - Grant # D64.40 - Princeton University: African Demographic Program (Box 58, Folder 938)
    - Grant # D64.41 - Population Reference Bureau: General Purposes (Box 58, Folder 939)
    - Grant # T64.42 - National Research Council, Thailand: Pilot Family Planning Project (Box 58, Folder 940-941)
    - Grant # T64.43 - F.P.A. of Hong Kong: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 942)
    - Grant # T64.44 - Columbia University: Preparation of Instructional Material (Box 58, Folder 943-944)
    - Grant # T64.45 - IUCD Conference, NY: Financing (Box 58, Folder 945)
    - Grant # T64.46: Acquisition of Patent Rights for IUD's (Box 58, Folder 946)
    - Grant # M64.47 - Delaware League for Planned Parenthood: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 947)
    - Grant # M64.48 - NY Medical College: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 948)
    - Grant # M64.49 - Columbia University: Gynecological Complaints in Previously Fertile Women (Box 58, Folder 949)
    - Grant # M64.50 - University of California - S.F.: IUCD Effects (Box 58, Folder 950)
    - Grant # M64.51 - University of Colorado: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 951)
    - Grant # M64.52 - Columbia University: Cytological Evaluation of IUCD (Box 58, Folder 952)
    - Grant # M64.53 - Albert Einstein College of Medicine: IUCD Acceptability Studies (Box 58, Folder 953)
    - Grant # M64.54 - Columbia University: Polyethylene Studies (Box 58, Folder 954)
    - Grant # M64.55 - Columbia University: IUCD Studies (Box 58, Folder 955)
    - Grant # M64.56 - NCMH: IUCD Evaluation (Box 58, Folder 956)
    - Grant # M64.57 - Temple University: Gametes Study (Box 58, Folder 957)
    - Grant # M64.58 - Tohu University, Japan: Tubal Occlusion Studies (Box 58, Folder 958)
    - Grant # M64.59 - V.A. Hospital, California (Long Beach): Hormonal Regulation Studies (Box 58, Folder 959)
    - Grant # M64.60 - University of Montreal: Physiology of Reproduction Studies (Box 58, Folder 960)